{
  "apikey": "%PUT-YOUR-API-KEY-HERE%",
  "description": "This is simple calibration data used for testing purposes. Do not use it in production environment!",
  "copyright": "Copyright (C) 2238 by BanAN Technologies Inc.",
  "test-data": [
    {
      "question": "28 + 82",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 90",
      "answer": 145
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 5",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "41 + 60",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 47",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "72 + 60",
      "answer": 132
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 39",
      "answer": 85
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 5",
      "answer": 98
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 96",
      "answer": 179
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 9",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 57",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "47 + 78",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 35",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 12",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "55 + 22",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 8",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 97",
      "answer": 182
    },
    {
      "question": "83 + 46",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "question": "63 + 16",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 74",
      "answer": 119
    },
    {
      "question": "4 + 5",
      "answer": 9
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 14",
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "question": "76 + 27",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "38 + 63",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "13 + 41",
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "question": "33 + 43",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 72",
      "answer": 111
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 35",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 51",
      "answer": 143
    },
    {
      "question": "95 + 15",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 39",
      "answer": 106
    },
    {
      "question": "31 + 61",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "16 + 87",
      "answer": 103
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 49",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "1 + 46",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "2 + 26",
      "answer": 28
    },
    {
      "question": "82 + 10",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 68",
      "answer": 124
    },
    {
      "question": "7 + 100",
      "answer": 107
    },
    {
      "question": "12 + 37",
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 97",
      "answer": 189
    },
    {
      "question": "96 + 82",
      "answer": 178
    },
    {
      "question": "39 + 15",
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "question": "46 + 5",
      "answer": 51
    },
    {
      "question": "5 + 77",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 44",
      "answer": 94
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 82",
      "answer": 126
    },
    {
      "question": "25 + 59",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "73 + 23",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 48",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 14",
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "question": "87 + 87",
      "answer": 174
    },
    {
      "question": "90 + 48",
      "answer": 138
    },
    {
      "question": "15 + 2",
      "answer": 17
    },
    {
      "question": "99 + 10",
      "answer": 109
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 35",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "question": "56 + 61",
      "answer": 117
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 84",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 81",
      "answer": 149
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 9",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "68 + 96",
      "answer": 164
    },
    {
      "question": "14 + 30",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "question": "37 + 88",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "57 + 20",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 41",
      "answer": 61
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 54",
      "answer": 74
    },
    {
      "question": "84 + 66",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 90",
      "answer": 182
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 31",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "93 + 89",
      "answer": 182
    },
    {
      "question": "80 + 30",
      "answer": 110
    },
    {
      "question": "45 + 26",
      "answer": 71
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 50",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 5",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "question": "32 + 26",
      "answer": 58
    },
    {
      "question": "58 + 11",
      "answer": 69
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 21",
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "question": "78 + 98",
      "answer": 176
    },
    {
      "question": "77 + 93",
      "answer": 170
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 42",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "74 + 27",
      "answer": 101
    },
    {
      "question": "6 + 75",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "question": "85 + 3",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "question": "20 + 27",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 29",
      "answer": 55
    },
    {
      "question": "21 + 75",
      "answer": 96
    },
    {
      "question": "30 + 52",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "question": "29 + 62",
      "answer": 91
    },
    {
      "question": "92 + 8",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "question": "67 + 17",
      "answer": 84
    },
    {
      "question": "26 + 49",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "question": "51 + 74",
      "answer": 125
    },
    {
      "question": "100 + 89",
      "answer": 189
    },
    {
      "question": "49 + 79",
      "answer": 128
    },
    {
      "question": "50 + 100",
      "answer": 150
    },
    {
      "question": "43 + 96",
      "answer": 139
    },
    {
      "question": "35 + 38",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "question": "97 + 11",
      "answer": 108
    },
    {
      "question": "62 + 15",
      "answer": 77
    },
    {
      "question": "44 + 11",
      "answer": 55
    }
  ],
  "chunk": {
    "number": 17,
    "total": 22,
    "size": 100,
    "range": {
      "from": 1600,
      "to": 1700
    }
  }
}